{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874748019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874748019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874748973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874748973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874749550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874749550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874755657","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874755657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874756178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874756178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874759882","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874759881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874760252","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874760252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874766445","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874766445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874773664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874773663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874780346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874780345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874781195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874781195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874787403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874787403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874793572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874793572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874794341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874794341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874794965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874794965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874796136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874796136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874799449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874799449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874800776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874800776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874806904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874806903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874808314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874808313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874809484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874809484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874815629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874815628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874816483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874816483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874821919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874821919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874823919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874823919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874830150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874830150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874830706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874830706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874836834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874836834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874837381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874837381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874842547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874842546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874848527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874848527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874855990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874855990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874856811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874856810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874863077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874863076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874869360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874869360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874870181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874870180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874876541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874876541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874877071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874877071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874883295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874883294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874884663","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874884662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874890247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874890247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874896768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874896768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874903052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874903052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874905147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874905146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874913612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874913612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874913739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874913739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874931069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874931069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 59474a6b-70a3-4a43-a18f-bd7fbb70e090"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874944013","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874944012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874949746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874949746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874950952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874950952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874951629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874951629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874952876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874952876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_imejaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874956416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874956416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874957314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874957314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874963522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874963522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874969636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874969635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874976067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874976067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874976827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874976827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874983027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874983026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874984173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874984173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874984933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874984933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maharage"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ge"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874991416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874991416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874992074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874992073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874992716","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874992716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874993322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874993322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874996461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874996461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874997034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874997033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874997341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874997341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549874998436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549874998436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anacheza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875000771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875000771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875001172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875001172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875002362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875002362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875003046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875003046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875004055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875004055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875010425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875010425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875011212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875011212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875014557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875014557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875014941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875014941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875015625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875015625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875016284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875016284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875022697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875022697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875023570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875023570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875026735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875026735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875027503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875027503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875027855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875027854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875033875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875033875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875034697","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875034696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875040845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875040845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875041908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875041908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875044543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875044543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875045599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875045599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875052006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875052006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875052340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875052340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875058547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875058547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875059702","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875059702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875062979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875062979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875063713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875063713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875064466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875064466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875065640","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875065640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875066468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875066467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875069366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875069366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875070247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875070247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ge"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875070701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875070701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ge"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875077671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875077670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ge"," userResponse":" ge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875078193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875078193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875084420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875084419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875085173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875085172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875087387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875087387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" c92128e5-352a-4ded-a8fb-aba7fc308403"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ogelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875101161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875101161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875101387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875101387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875102357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875102356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875103636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875103636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875106493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875106493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875107337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875107336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875107650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875107649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875108882","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875108882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875112386","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875112386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875113372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875113372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875113626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875113626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875114575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875114575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875117407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875117407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875118440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875118440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875118916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875118916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875123449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875123449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875123597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875123597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0fe7c792-80b5-4657-bf88-8132814eadd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875168989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875168988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875187288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875187288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875200252","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875200252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875208465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875208464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875214844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875214844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875215306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875215306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875215794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875215794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875216008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875216007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_akalala"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875220080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875220080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875226935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875226935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875227777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875227777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875237793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875237793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875244405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875244405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875245012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875245012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ti"," userResponse":" ti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875245611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875245611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875251838","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875251838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875252993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875252993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tikitimaji"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875262973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875262973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwa"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875264310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875264309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mwa"," userResponse":" nzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875270656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875270656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" mwa"," userResponse":" mwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875271588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875271587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875272623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875272623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" nzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875278944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875278944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875279834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875279834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nzi"," userResponse":" nzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875285869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875285868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875292237","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875292237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875298953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875298953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875305446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875305446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875311981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875311981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875312734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875312734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875313359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875313358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875319826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875319826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875320510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875320510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875321374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875321374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875325156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875325155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875325866","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875325866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875332264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875332264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875332906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875332906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875333522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875333522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875339749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875339749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875340408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875340408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875341289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875341289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875345943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875345943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875353925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875353924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" su"," userResponse":" su"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875354873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875354873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875361033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875361032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875361632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875361632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875362196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875362196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sufuria"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875370409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875370409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875376585","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875376585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875382813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875382813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875388904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875388904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875395038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875395038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875401156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875401156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875402233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875402233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875408188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875408187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875414398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875414398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875415784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875415784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875423793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875423793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875424972","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875424971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875434145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875434145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875440287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875440286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875440817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875440817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875441348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875441348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875441869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875441869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875442468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875442468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875445539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875445539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875446113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875446112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875446609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875446609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875452863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875452863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875453813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875453813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875456380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875456380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875456918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875456918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875457546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875457546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" cha"," userResponse":" cha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875458587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875458586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875459177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875459177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875461452","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875461451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" b36e3c00-4345-4ad9-9fdf-551c9229dcb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875469930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875469930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0b1d79d6-d354-42a7-90c3-9aa3ac9ca687"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875477400","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875477400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 0b1d79d6-d354-42a7-90c3-9aa3ac9ca687"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875493854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875493854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 184c820c-b1cb-4981-86b1-c1c5d0e40870"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875495480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875495479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 184c820c-b1cb-4981-86b1-c1c5d0e40870"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875502769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875502769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 184c820c-b1cb-4981-86b1-c1c5d0e40870"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875521902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875521901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875524907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875524907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875526446","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875526446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875526880","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875526880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875527074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875527074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875527579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875527579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875530230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875530230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875531934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875531934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875534071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875534071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875536001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875536001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875538155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875538155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875538729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875538729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875538913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875538913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875539668","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875539668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875544038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875544038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875546496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875546496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875548953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875548953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875551130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875551130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875553035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875553035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875553810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875553809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875559912","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875559912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875562430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875562430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875564720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875564720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875565935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875565935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875566370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875566370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875567124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875567124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875573003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875573003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875575075","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875575075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875577422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875577422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875579865","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875579865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875581746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875581746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875583192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875583192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875583640","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875583640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875586571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875586570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875589269","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875589269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875591563","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875591563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875593312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875593312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875593672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875593671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875594626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875594626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875595112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875595112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875595987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875595987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875600783","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875600782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875602642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875602642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875604482","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875604481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875606999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875606999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875609086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875609086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875610993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875610993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875611847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875611846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875612501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875612501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875613605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875613605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875619463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875619462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875621521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875621521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875623170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875623169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875625233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875625233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875627833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875627833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875628270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875628270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875628399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875628399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875669650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875669650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" a1bcae7c-5e40-4a58-853a-47fabc0c9b77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875684710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875684710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875690870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875690870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875691409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875691409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875697544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875697544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875698494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875698494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875699393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875699393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875702150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875702149"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875702756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875702756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875703423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875703423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875709721","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875709720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875710670","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875710670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875711158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875711158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875714678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875714677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875721138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875721138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875733877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875733876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875735914","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875735913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875741852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875741852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875743064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875743063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875746056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875746056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875747175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875747175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549875753636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549875753636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_103657"," gameId":" 3ab2fefe-48bc-453f-b612-2ff02b34e802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pundamilia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}